{
    "subject": "Francis_I_of_the_Two_Sicilies",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Archduchess_Maria_Clementina_of_Austria",
    "human_readable": "Francis I of the Two Sicilies is married to Archduchess Maria Clementina of Austria.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.958641529083252,
            "question": "Who was Francis I of the Two Sicilies married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9342855215072632,
            "question": "Who was the husband of Archduchess Maria Clementina of Austria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9035106897354126,
            "question": "What was Archduchess Maria Clementina of Austria's role in her marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.847169816493988,
            "question": "How might the marriage of Francis I and Archduchess Maria Clementina have impacted the political landscape of Europe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7738953232765198,
            "question": "Where was Archduchess Maria Clementina of Austria from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7522033452987671,
            "question": "To which royal family did Francis I of the Two Sicilies belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6307680010795593,
            "question": "In which century did Francis I of the Two Sicilies reign?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4479314684867859,
            "question": "What title did Archduchess Maria Clementina hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26090332865715027,
            "question": "Can you name another European monarch who married into a different royal family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.060849629342556,
            "question": "What were some common motivations for arranged marriages in royal families?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Francis I of the Two Sicilies is married to Archduchess Maria Clementina of Austria.",
            "html": "yago_23862_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name another European monarch who married into a different royal family?",
            "html": "yago_23862_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What title did Archduchess Maria Clementina hold?",
            "html": "yago_23862_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which century did Francis I of the Two Sicilies reign?",
            "html": "yago_23862_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23862_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23862_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23862_136.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23862_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23862_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23862_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23862_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23862_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23862_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23862_64.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple query is \"Francis I of the Two Sicilies is married to Archduchess Maria Clementina of Austria.\" \n\nGiven the context information:\n\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_23862/re-ranker-msmarco/96.txt, it is stated that \"spouse =Maria Clementina of Austria\" and also mentioned as Francis I (\"Francesco Gennaro Giuseppe\", August 14, 1777 &ndash; November 8, 1830) was King of the Two Sicilies from 1825 to 1830.\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_23862/re-ranker-msmarco/100.txt, it is stated that \"In 1796 Francis married his double first cousin Archduchess Maria Clementina of Austria\".\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_23862/re-ranker-msmarco/63.txt and file_path: /Users/stafanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_23862/re-ranker-msmarco/96.txt, it is mentioned that Francis I married Archduchess Maria Clementina of Austria.\n\nTherefore, the answer should be:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide clear information that Francis I of the Two Sicilies was indeed married to Archduchess Maria Clementina of Austria. This can be seen from the details in multiple files, such as the birth and early life section indicating their marriage in 1796, and further specifying her as his double first cousin."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}